Guide to the Frank Baker papers, 1641-2002 and undated, bulk 1740-1995 RL.00069
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1641-1999 and undated, 122 boxes
  - Subject Files Series: Alphabetical Files II Subseries, 1736-1999 and undated, 14 boxes
    - Biographies, circa 1780s-1890s, Folders 1-2 of 12 (Box 116)
      Contents: Dr. Samuel Annesley; Joseph Barker; Edward Baines; Richard Baxter; Mary Brett; Emily Bronte; Jabez Bunting; John Bunyan; Elizabeth Burdsall; John Nelson; Cardinal Newman; Adam Clarke; George Clarke; Rev. Joseph Cockin; Samuel Taylor Coleridge; R. Costerdine; Joseph Cownley; Rev. John Crosse; Rev. Spedding Curwen; Samuel Drew; Christmas Evans; and Thomas Gandy.
    - Biographies, circa 1780s-1890s, Folders 3-7 of 12 (Box 117)
      Contents (continued from previous box): William Geden; Elizabeth Gellatly; Hugh Gilmore; Thomas Goldthorpe; Thomas Haigh; Thomas Hanby; Elizabeth Hannam; John Harrap; Jane Vizell Hazell; Samuel Hick; John Hickling; Rev. Thomas Hartwell Horne; John Jackson; Rev. W. Jay; William Johnson; Matthias Joyce; William Keer; Simon Kilham; Rev. Joel Abraham Knight; Thomas Lee; John Leifchild; Rev. G. C. Maitland; Johnathon Maskew; John Mason; Ann Mather; Timothy Richard Matthews; Rev. Colin C. McKechinie; Methodist Magazine, 1818 (various); James Montgomery; Rev. John Newton; Laurence Oliphant; Gideon Ouseley; George Osborn; Mary Ann Parkinson; and Thomas Parson.
    - Biographies, circa 1780s-1890s, Folders 7-12 of 12 (Box 118)
      Contents (continued from previous box): John Pawson; Thomas Payne; Christopher Peacock; M. Pendleton; Thomas Pendleton; John Prickard; Robert Raikes; Richard Rodda; Sarah Savage; Selina, Countess of Huntingdon; Rev. John Smith; William Smith; Sampson Staniforth; John Story; Rev. Thomas Stratten; J. S. Sutcliffe; William Taylor; Silas Told; Juan de Valides; Samuel Walker; Charles Wesley; John Wesley; Wesleyan-Methodist Magazine, 1877 (various); Rev. George Whitefield; William Williams; Duncan Wright; and Miscellaneous.
    - Book plates, 1799-1940 and undated (Box 118)
      Approximately sixty book plates, the scrapbook pages from which they have loosened, and printed material on this topic.
    - Bookroom inventory, 1791, 1950, and 1984, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 118)
      Contains photocopy of original manuscript of "An Inventory of the Books, Tracts, Pamphlets &c belonging to the Late Reverend John Wesley," 1791; and Baker's notes on the compilation of three indexes to the inventory in alphabetical, union catalog, and bibliographic order.
    - Bookroom inventory, 1791, 1950, and 1984, Folders 2-4 of 4 (Box 119)
    - Broadsheets and circular letters (photocopies), 1750-1834 and undated, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Bysshe (Edward?)--Art of Poetry, subject headings and related words, undated (Box 119)
    - The Christian Library--three notebooks by Baker, undated, 250 pages (Box 119)
    - Church Methodists, undated (Box 119)
    - Churton, Edward, 1800-1874 (Box 119)
    - Cokesbury United Methodist Church, undated (Box 119)
    - A Concordance to the Book of Common Prayer, According to the Use of the Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America, by J. Courtney Jones, 1898 [photocopy] (Box 119)
    - Currituck County, N.C. - Church Book of Mount Zion Methodist Episcopal Church, 1972 and undated (Box 120)
    - Dr. Williams' Library, 1936-1946 (Box 120)
    - Early American Methodism, 1807, 1855, 1954-1984, and undated, 2 folders (Box 120)
      Articles and unpublished research by Baker and other authors on early American Methodism. Baker titles gathered here include: Let's Start an Argument, 1962; The Beginnings of American Methodism, 1963; When Did Methodism Begin? 1963; 'Come over and Help Us' -- America to Wesley, 1971; John Wesley and America, 1984; and The Status of Methodist Preachers in America, 1769-1791, 1985.
    - Early Methodist Ephemera, 1791-1833 (Box 120)
    - Ephemera--JW, 1750-1790 and undated (Box 120)
    - Ephemera--non-Wesley, undated (Box 120)
      Includes a disparate variety of ephemera collected by Frank Baker, including tickets to the Jubilee, June 1887; a ticket to a ship-launching (Thunderer, 1831); a small booklet summarizing The Pilgrim's Progress, that originally accompanied a card-game; a very tiny Victorian-era photographic stamp depicting an unidentified family in a formal group portrait; and a circulation bookplate from the Hull Subscription Library, 1775.
    - Epworth Press, 1953 and undated (Box 120)
    - Evangelical Library, 1947-1960 and undated (Box 120)
    - Fragments--manuscript and printed fragments and clippings, 1902, 1906, 1913, 1926, 1942, 1951, and undated (Box 120)
      Miscellaneous manuscript and print fragments found by Enid Hickingbotham, Dr. Baker's daughter, after his death; removed from various books into which they had been inserted.
    - The Gentleman's Magazine: Index to the Books to the End of the Fifty-Sixth Volume, 1787 (Box 120)
    - Historical slides, John Street United Methodist Church, undated (Box 120)
    - Hull and Yorkshire--circuit plans, conference photographs, and other documents, 1829, 1851, 1956, 1981, and undated (Box 120)
    - Irving Collection, 1819-1842, 1956 (Box 120)
    - John Rylands University Library - notes on manuscript collection, undated (Box 121)
    - Knowlwood Circuit, 1848 (Box 121)
    - Locke, John, 1983 and undated (Box 121)
    - Marriott, Thomas: British Methodist Circuit Plans Collection, 1825-1826 (Box 121)
      Photocopy made for Frank Baker, some time in the 1960s to 1980s. The original collection and copyright to it are held by the General Commission on Archives and History of the Methodist Church, Drew University. This folder contains the guide to the collection, published by the GCAH in 2004, and several pages of typewritten notes made by Baker. The photocopies of the circuit plans themselves have been removed to Oversize Materials.
    - Maslen, K. I. D., The Bowyer Ledgers: the Printing Accounts of William Bowyer Father and Son, with a Checklist of Bowyer Printing, 1699-1777, 1991 (Box 121)
    - Methodist bibliography, rough outline, circa, 1941-1949 (Box 121)
    - Methodist book classifications, undated (Box 121)
    - Methodist diary at High Wycombe, 1777 (Box 121)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 121)
    - The Newcastle General Magazine (photocopy), 1747 (Box 121)
    - North Carolina Church History, 1982-1983, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Norwich, undated (Box 121)
    - Notebooks--see Research notes, various topics (bound) (Box 121)
    - Notts University, undated (Box 121)
    - Osborne, Richard H., 1700s, 1992, and undated (Box 121)
      Correspondence with Baker and photocopies of three manuscript sermons, 1700s-1800s.
    - Prior, Matthew--index to poems, undated (Box 121)
    - Research notes, various topics (loose), 1736-1777, 1817-1822, 1896, 1945-1993, and undated, Folders 1-5 of 10 (Box 122)
      Bibliography, notes, photocopies, and transcriptions on a wide variety of topics, received loose in various boxes and gathered here. Topics included, but are not limited to, the following: CW's hymns; John Fane; JW and newspapers; JW as educator; JW's philosophical thought; Wesley family traditions; Wesley family tree; the Wesleys and the coronations. Related items are clipped or batched together, but otherwise these folders are unarranged.
    - Research notes, various topics (loose), 1736-1777, 1817-1822, 1896, 1945-1993, and undated, Folders 6-10 of 10 (Box 123)
    - Research notes, bound notebooks, undated, Folders 1-6 of 19 (Box 124)
      Notebooks on various topics, including: Armenian Magazine (5 notebooks), Children (1 notebook), Libraries and Archives (16 notebooks), Moravianism (1 notebook), Publications, (5 notebooks), Reading (7 notebooks).
    - Research notes, bound notebooks, undated, Folders 7-15 of 19 (Box 125)
    - Research notes, bound notebooks, undated, Folders 16-19 of 19 (Box 126)
    - Slavery, 1765-1787, 1970-1984, and undated, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Small collections, 1827-1950 (Box 126)
    - Spencer, William, 1764-1797, 1975 (Box 126)
    - St. Martin's Review, 1938 (Box 126)
    - Steadman, Melvin, L., partial card catalog of his Methodist collection, 1988-1989 (Box 126)
    - Taylor, Jeremy, 1968, 1988 (Box 126)
    - To be indexed--notes on various topics and articles from Wesleyan Methodist Magazine, 1851-1898 and undated (Box 126)
    - Union Catalogue Files, 1746-1999, 10 folders (Box 127)
      Copies of Wesley's works on which Baker or his colleagues did research, arranged by Union Catalogue number. Materials appear to constitute part of a filing system FB used for various purposes. In particular there is some work on Charles Wesley here, mainly correspondence and manuscripts exchanged with S. T. Kimbrough in preparation for a 1995 Charles Wesley Society conference on CW's Hymns on the Lord's Supper and an edition of his Hymns for Ascension-Day.. There are also typescripts and photocopies materials similar to many found in the Wesley Works Archive.
    - Walker, William--various writings on Settle and Baker's notes, 1900 and undated (Box 127)
    - Wesley and Seabury, undated (Box 128)
    - Wesley Anniversaries and Celebrations (1953, 1988), 1953, 1977-1988, 4 folders (Box 128)
      Correspondence, services, articles, printed materials, and other items.
    - Wesley's preachers, undated, 2 folders (Box 128)
      Alphabetical index, circa 250 pages, of more than 600 18th-century preachers. Each entry lists preacher's stations in chronological order, followed by citations for the sources of this information. Undated but probably prepared in the late 1970s or 1980s, by Baker and Enid Hickingbotham (his daughter). Related material, including this index at other stages of its composition, can be found under "British Preachers' Stationing, 1744-1764" in the Wesley Works Archive, Methodist Societies Series, Minutes Subseries.
    - Wesley's sermon register, 1991 and undated (Box 128)
    - West Riding, trust deeds and trustees of chapels, undated (Box 128)
  - Subject Files Series: Wesley Family Files Subseries, 1692-1997 and undated, 10 boxes
    Family members are identified here by their relationship to JW (1703-1791) and/or Charles Wesley (1707-1788), cited as JW or CW, respectively. In addition to FB's correspondence, notes, and printed materials, many folders contain extensive transcriptions and photocopies of original manuscript letters, journals, and writings by Wesley family members. Original manuscript items and many 18th and 19th century engravings present in these folders are being transferred to the Frank Baker Collection of Wesleyana and British Methodism, in most cases to the Wesley Family Series. Separation sheets and, where feasible, photocopies of originals have been left in the folders in this subseries. Subseries is arranged by family member, chronologically by date of birth, with a concluding folder group of various topics.
    - Samuel Wesley, Sr. (1662-1735)
      Church of England clergyman, poet, and father of JW and CW. Folder group contains many transcriptions of his letters from various manuscript sources.
      - Correspondence, notes, and printed materials, circa late 1600s, 1806-1808, 1826, 1875, 1904, 1931-1979, and undated (Box 129)
      - Letters--handwritten transcriptions, 1705-1707 (Box 129)
        Undated transcriptions, perhaps early 20th century, from and to Samuel Wesley, 1705-1707. Labeled as from "Diaries of Thomas Hearne" and "Ballard MSS. 34 and 35."
      - Letters--typed transcriptions, 1692-1734-1707 (Box 129)
        Approximately thirty transcriptions mainly by FB. Includes transcription of Samuel Wesley ALS to Justice Hook, 1700 July 10, from holograph ALS in Frank Baker Collection of Wesleyana and British Methodism.
      - Portraits--engravings, 1808 and undated (Box 129)
        One engraving with accompanying verse caption by Samuel Wesley.
      - Wesley manuscripts--mainly Samuel Wesley and Susanna, 1700-1709, 1740, 1880, and undated (Box 129)
      - Writings--manuscript photocopies, 1705-1707, 1732, and undated (Box 129)
    - Susannah Wesley (1669-1742)
      - Articles, notes, and printed materials, 1709, 1742, 1852, 1953-1982, and undated (Box 129)
        Includes FB articles Susannah Wesley, Apologist for Methodism and Salute to Susannah.
      - Correspondence, 1933, 1948-1989 (Box 129)
      - Elizabeth Hart research on SW, 1981-1993 (Box 129)
        Includes Hart articles Susannah Wesley and the Editors (1988) and Susannah Annesley Wesley--an Able Divine (1988). Includes FB article Susannah Wesley, Puritan (1981).
      - Elizabeth Lynch research on SW, 1984, 1994 (Box 129)
      - Letters--facsimiles, photocopies, and transcriptions, 1702-1741, 1852-1866, 1933-1989, and undated (Box 129)
        Circa thirty-five letters from various archival and printed sources.
      - Marmaduke Riggall research and notes on SW, 1741, 1911-1929, and undated (Box 129)
        Includes Riggall's transcription, circa 1921, of Some Remarks on a Letter from the Reverend Mr. Whitefield to the Reverend Mr. Wesley..., 1741, which he attributes to SW in extensive notes.
      - Portraits and engravings, 1957 and undated (Box 129)
        Engravings to 1800s, including "Susanna Wesley Addressing the Rustics at Epworth Rectory."
      - Susanna Wesley's house, 1947-1948, 1974, and 1988 (Box 129)
    - Samuel Wesley, Jr. (1690-1739)
      Eldest brother of JW and CW.
      - Correspondence, notes, and letters (photocopies and transcriptions), 1714-1739, 1812, 1904, 1945, 1974, 1991, and undated, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Susanna (Wesley) Ellison (1695-1764)
      An elder sister of JW and CW.
      - Correspondence and family tree, 1955-1958 (Box 130)
    - Mehitabel (Hetty Wesley) Wright (1697-1750)
      Poet and elder sister of JW and CW.
      - Correspondence, notes, letters (photocopies and transcriptions), 1728-1749, 1948-1985 (Box 130)
    - Anne (Wesley) Lambert (b. 1702)
      - Correspondence, 1741-1746 (Box 130)
    - John Wesley (1703-1791)
      Correspondence, notes, printed materials, and numerous photocopies and transcriptions of manuscript material from various sources. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
      - Anecdotes, 1948 and undated (Box 130)
      - Biography, 1956, 1975, and undated (Box 130)
      - Cathedral Cities, 1982 and undated (Box 130)
      - Churchmanship, 1730-1784, 1894, 1967-1968, and undated (Box 130)
      - Conversion, 1962 and undated (Box 130)
      - Deeds and indentures, 1976 (Box 130)
      - Diaries, 1725-1738, 1976 (Box 130)
        Includes pamphlet Selections from the Early Manuscript Diaries and Writings of JW and the Oxford Methodists, 1725-1738, undated.
      - Diary excerpts--miscellaneous, 1724-1735 (Box 130)
      - Film, 1953-1955 (Box 130)
      - Filmstrips, 1952 and undated (Box 130)
      - Forgeries, Lithos, etc., 1741, 1771-1790, 1839, 1922, 1933-1936, 1955-1958, 1976, 1984, and undated (Box 130)
      - Handwriting, 1981, 1991 (Box 130)
        Includes Three Tests and a Key: Identifying JW's Handwriting," by Richard P. Heitzenrater, 1981.
      - Handwriting: JW's handwriting throughout his life, 1738-1746, 1756-1791, and undated (Box 130)
        Contains circa fifty photocopied manuscript letters.
      - Humor of, 1774, 1784, 1973, and undated (Box 130)
      - Hymns--manuscripts, 1773, 1886, 1974, 1982, and undated (Box 130)
        Photocopy of Old St. George's manuscript, 1773, and of George Osborn cover letter, 1886.
      - Itinerary, 1744-1745 (Box 130)
      - Journals, diaries, and cipher, 1732-1791, 1915-1918, 1952-1959, and undated (Box 130)
      - Journal, Memos, undated (Box 131)
      - Leisure, health, haste and hurry, etc., 1740-1785, 1825, 1898, 1946-1959, 1988-1989, and undated (Box 131)
      - Letterbook, 1724-1729 (Box 131)
      - Letters: FB correspondence and copies of JW letters from various collections, 1749-1790, 1809-1829, 1900-1974, and undated, 4 folders (Box 131)
        Folder sequence contains photocopies or transcriptions of some 70 JW letters, primarily from the Lamplough Collection, but also from the Historical Society of Pennsylvania and other collections. File on Lamplough Collection (Folder 4) also contains much 20th century provenance data about the auctioning and sales of individual letters, including correspondence from John Telford, editor of JW's letters. Material from Historical Society of Pennsylvania includes some letters of Samuel Wesley (1766-1837).
      - Letters: autograph photocopies, 1780-1790 and undated (Box 131)
      - Letters: Clayton, John, to JW, 1732 Sept. 5 (Box 131)
        Unsigned handwritten transcription labeled "Stampe Col: Holy Club." Possibly transcribed by George Stampe, early 20th century.
      - Letters: to Aspasia (Mrs. Mary Pendarves) and to Selima (Anne Granville), 1730-1732, and undated (Box 131)
      - Letters: Wesley, Charles, from Nelson notebook, 1755-1756 (Box 131)
        Photocopies and notes from John Nelson notebook, Methodist Archives MS. 170, including Ought We to Separate from the Church of England.
        Related materials: other photocopies of MS. 170, which may cover different portions, can be found in the Wesley Works Archive, Letters Series, Letters by Archive.
      - Library, 1955 and undated (Box 131)
      - Manuscripts--notes and corrections to JW's holdings, circa 1727-1750 and undated (Box 131)
        Contains partial copies of Colman diary, 1737, and "A Compendium of Bartholin's Physicks," 1737.
      - Memory for dates, undated (Box 131)
      - Miscellaneous, 1893, 1951-1977, and undated (Box 131)
      - Miscellany verses, transcribed from Colman Collection, Vol. I, 1730 and undated (Box 131)
      - Mrs. JW, 1750-1758, 1779-1781, 1863, 1924, 1947-1952, 1990, and undated (Box 132)
      - Notebooks--photocopy and transcription from Wesley's House (Dodsworth Bequest), 1722-1723 (Box 132)
      - Notebooks--photocopy from State Library of Victoria, 1746-1747 (Box 132)
      - Ordinations, 1817, 1819, and undated (Box 132)
      - Other People Named, 1741, 1951 and 1974 (Box 132)
      - Poetry, 1970 (Box 132)
      - Practical Divinity, 1762-1765, 1986, 2 folders (Box 132)
        For possibly related material, see also the various folders on Practical Divinity in Writings and Research Series, Other Publications Subseries.
      - Private devotions--notes on Colman Collection, Vol 8, undated (Box 132)
      - Quotations, 1763 and undated (Box 132)
      - Quotations: self-quotations, undated (Box 132)
      - Sayings, 1915, 1948-1953, 1980, 1992-1994, and undated (Box 132)
      - Sermons, 1925, 1945-1963, and undated (Box 132)
        Contains draft of FB article Wesley's Sermons, 1945.
      - Shipley, The Theology of JW: A Selected Bibliography, undated (Box 132)
      - Spelling Sermons, undated (Box 132)
      - Theology, 1951, 1960-1961 (Box 132)
      - Travel, 1977 (Box 132)
      - Tributes to JW, 1789-1791, 1918, and undated (Box 132)
        Includes pamphlet excerpted from The Weekly Entertainer, 1791 Sept. 12; and transcription, 1918, of comments attributed to The Eccentricities of John Edwin, Comedian..., 1791.
      - Wesley and His Wife, 1752, 1781, 1898, 1937-1938, 1946-1947, 1980, and undated (Box 132)
        Includes Methodist Recorder clippings circa 1898 with one facsimile and several print reproductions of letters JW wrote to his wife.
      - Wills, 1747, 1789, 1934, 1967, and undated (Box 132)
    - Martha (Wesley) Hall (1706-1791) (Box 133)
      Sister of JW and CW, between them in age. In Samuel Johnson's circle later in life.
      - Correspondence, notes, letters (photocopies and transcriptions), 1724-1734, 1749, 1764, 1850, 1898, 1955, and undated (Box 133)
        Includes two Methodist Recorder clippings circa 1898 with one facsimile and several print reproductions of letters by Martha Wesley.
    - Charles Wesley (1707-1788)
      - Accounts, undated (Box 133)
      - Anniversaries and commemorations, 1907-1957, 2 folders (Box 133)
        Pamphlets, programs, and other printed materials from services on various anniversaries of Charles Wesley's birth or death. Includes pamphlets Bi-Centenary of the Birth of Charles Wesley: 1707-1907; Old Marylebone and Some of Its Famous People: The Brownings, Charles Dickens, Charles Wesley, Lord Nelson, Lord Byron, Francis Bacon; and The Old Church Garden, St. Marylebone, London, 1400-1951.
      - Beckerlegge, Oliver, Charles Wesley's Vocabulary, 1968 (Box 133)
      - Bristol Methodist Council--FB address, 1953-1955 (Box 133)
      - Charles Wesley Publication Colloquium, Princeton Theological Seminary, 1989 Sept. 22-24 (Box 133)
      - Charles Wesley's Publishing Programme--FB lecture, adapted from article, 1989, 1992 (Box 133)
      - Dictionary articles on, 1983 and undated (Box 133)
      - General correspondence (FB), 1946-1962 and undated (Box 133)
        Contains unauthenticated Charles Wesley and JW autograph fragments.
      - General notes and research, 1735-1788, 1908, 1947-1994, and undated (Box 133)
        Contains: photocopied manuscript journal, 1751; transcribed letters and documents, 1735-1786; manuscript anecdote, Charles Wesley - An Affaire de Coeur, by B.A. Hurd Barley, 1908; and a FB article Charles Wesley in Ireland, 1947.
      - Homes and Property, 1770, 1932, 1950 (Box 133)
        Contains transcription of letter, Rebecca Gwynne to Sarah (Gwynne) Wesley, 1770 Dec. 3. Also contains pamphlet Charles Wesley's House: Bristol, 1749-1771, undated.
      - Hymns: General correspondence and notes, 1913, 1957, 1987-1991, and undated (Box 133)
      - Hymns: singing festivals, 1957, 1962 (Box 133)
      - Hymns: Manuscript photocopies and photographs, various sources, 1748-1788, 1959, and undated (Box 133)
      - Hymns: Printed material--articles and pamphlets by various authors, 1956-1957 and undated (Box 133)
      - Journals: Correspondence, FB and others, 1888, 1970 (Box 133)
      - Journals: Photocopies, 1736-1771, Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box 133)
      - Journals: Photocopies, 1736-1771, Folders 3-4 of 4 (Box 134)
      - Journals: Transcriptions, notes, and printed materials, 1739-1758 and undated (Box 134)
      - Journals: letters, 1734-1756, 1988-1992 (Box 134)
        [Photocopies of oversize journal pages, ca. 1740-1756, removed to Oversize Materials.]
      - Lecture on Charles Wesley as Revealed by His Letters (1948, Hart58), 1948-1956 (Box 134)
      - Letters: Charles Wesley's Letters--address by FB, 1749, 1782, 1790, 1983-1989, and undated (Box 134)
      - Letters: CW--a summary, circa 1736-1789, 1974-1996, and undated, 2 folders (Box 134)
        FB correspondence, notes, and detailed chronologies of CW letters, ca. 1724-1788, plus numerous photocopies and transcriptions.
      - Letters: Fletcher, John--chronologies and printed material, 1746-1756, 1989, and undated (Box 134)
      - Letters: Hastings, Selina, Countess of Huntingdon--chronology of 100 letters to CW from 1742-1775, undated (Box 135)
      - Letters: Letter from Georgia -- Including FB's Charles Wesley to 'Varanese' and 'Varanese' to Charles Wesley (1946, Hart37), 1736 and undated (Box 135)
      - Letters: Various, to CW, 1756-1783, 1986-1992 (Box 135)
      - Letters: Whitefield, George, 1736, 1766-1770, 1993, and undated (Box 135)
        Letters to CW, transcribed.
      - Poems, 1741-1754, 1785-1786, 1909, 1939-1956, and undated, 3 folders (Box 135)
      - Scripture Cards, 1958 and undated (Box 135)
      - A Sermon Preached on Sunday, April 4, 1742, Before the University of Oxford, 1742, 1790, and 1966 (Box 135)
      - Sermons, 1736, 1816, and 1995 (Box 135)
      - Sons' Concerts, undated (Box 135)
      - Telford, John, The Life of Charles Wesley, M.A., undated (Box 135)
      - Treatise on the Lord's Supper, 1849, 1990-1991 and undated (Box 135)